[RANDOM NOISES]
HOUSEKEEPING, HOUSEKEEPING
♪ AHHHH! ♪
♪ I REMEMBER YOU
WAS CONFLICTED ♪
♪ MISUSING YOUR INFLUENCE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I DID THE SAME ♪
♪ ABUSING MY POWER FULL
OF RESENTMENT ♪
♪ RESENTMENT THAT TURNED
INTO A DEEP DEPRESSION ♪
♪ FOUND MYSELF SCREAMING
IN A HOTEL ROOM ♪
♪ AHHHH! ♪
♪ LUCIFER WAS
ALL AROUND ME ♪
♪ SO I KEPT RUNNING ♪
♪ UNTIL I FOUND MY SAFE HAVEN ♪
♪ I WAS TRYING TO CONVINCE
MYSELF THE STRIPES I GOT ♪
♪ MAKING MYSELF REALIZE WHAT
MY FOUNDATION WAS ♪
♪ IN THE ROOM
AND I RUN IT ♪
♪ AND I RUN IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ BUT WHILE MY LOVED
ONES WAS FIGHTING ♪
♪ A CONTINUOUS WAR
BACK IN THE CITY ♪
♪ I WAS ENTERING A NEW ONE ♪
♪ A WAR THAT WAS
BASED ON APARTHEID ♪
♪ AND DISCRIMINATION ♪
♪ A YO MAMA MY NIGGA ♪
♪ IMA BE THE GREATEST TO
EVER DO THIS SHIT ♪
♪ OH MY MAMA DON'T LIKE ♪
♪ ONLY DEAD HOMIES ♪
♪ AY SIDEWAY
TURN THAT SHIT UP NIGGA ♪
♪ TURN THAT SHIT UP ♪
♪ SIDEWAY
TURN THAT SHIT UP NIGGA ♪
♪ TELL ME WHO THE BITCH NIGGA
HATIN ON ME ♪
♪ JUMPING ON MY DICK
BUT THIS DICK AIN'T FREE ♪
♪ "TO PIMP A BUTTERFLY"
ANOTHER CLASSIC CD ♪
♪ GHETTO LULLABY FOR
EVERYONE THEY MC ♪
♪ BLOW! BLOW! BLOW! BLOW! ♪
♪ LOOKING AT RIP ♪
♪ MY DILIGENCE IS ONLY MEANT TO
WRITE YOUR EULOGY ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ALLS MY LIFE I HAS
TO FIGHT, NIGGA ♪
♪ ALLS MY LIFE I... ♪
♪ HARD TIMES LIKE, "GOD!" ♪
♪ BAD TRIPS LIKE, "YEA!" ♪
♪ NAZARETH, I'M FUCKED UP
HOMIE YOU FUCKED UP ♪
♪ BUT IF GOD GOT US
THEN WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT
NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU FEEL
ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ HUH? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU FEEL
ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ UH, AND WHEN I WAKE UP ♪
♪ I RECOGNIZE YOU'RE LOOKIN' AT
ME FOR THE PAY CUT ♪
♪ BUT HOMICIDE BE LOOKIN' AT
YOU FROM THE FACE DOWN ♪
♪ WHAT MAC-11 EVEN BOOM
WITH THE BASS DOWN ♪
♪ SCHEMIN', AND LET ME
TELL YOU 'BOUT MY LIFE ♪
♪ PAINKILLERS ONLY PUT ME
IN THE TWILIGHT ♪
♪ WHERE PRETTY PUSSY AND
BENJAMIN IS THE HIGHLIGHT ♪
♪ NOW TELL MY MOMMA I
LOVE HER BUT THIS WHAT
I LIKE, LORD KNOWS ♪
♪ 20 OF 'EM IN MY CHEVY, TELL
'EM ALL TO COME AND GET ME ♪
♪ REAPIN' EVERYTHING I SOW,
SO MY KARMA COME ♪
♪ AND HEAVEN NO PRELIMINARY
HEARING, SO FOR RECORD ♪
♪ I'M A MOTHERFUCKIN' GANGSTER
IN SILENCE FOR THE RECORD ♪
♪ TELL THE WORLD I
KNOW IT'S TOO LATE, ♪
♪ BOYS AND GIRLS,
I THINK I GONE CRAZY ♪
♪ DROWN INSIDE
MY VICES ALL DAY ♪
♪ WON'T YOU PLEASE
BELIEVE WHEN I SAY ♪
♪ WOULDN'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ WE BEEN HURT,
BEEN DOWN BEFORE ♪
♪ NIGGA
WHEN OUR PRIDE WAS LOW ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT THE WORLD LIKE,
"WHERE DO WE GO?" ♪
♪ NIGGA, AND WE HATE PO-PO ♪
♪ WANNA KILL US DEAD IN
THE STREET FO SHO ♪
♪ NIGGA,
I'M AT THE PREACHER'S DOOR ♪
♪ MY KNEES GETTIN' WEAK AND
MY GUN MIGHT BLOW ♪
♪ BUT WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT
NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU
FEEL ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ HUH? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU FEEL
ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANT,
YOU A HOUSE OR A CAR ♪
♪ 40 ACRES AND A MULE,
A PIANO, A GUITAR? ♪
♪ ANYTHING, SEE MY NAME
IS LUCY, I'M YOUR DOG ♪
♪ MOTHERFUCKER, YOU CAN
LIVE AT THE MALL ♪
♪ I CAN SEE THE EVIL, I CAN
TELL IT I KNOW IT'S ILLEGAL ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK ABOUT IT, I
DEPOSIT EVERY LITTLE ZERO ♪
♪ THINKIN OF MY PARTNER PUT THE
CANDY, PAINT IT ON THE REGAL ♪
♪ DIGGIN' IN MY POCKET AIN'T A
PROFIT BIG ENOUGH TO FEED YOU ♪
♪ EVERYDAY MY LOGIC, ♪
♪ GET ANOTHER DOLLAR
JUST TO KEEP YOU ♪
♪ IN THE PRESENCE OF YOUR
CHICO... AH! ♪
♪ I DON'T TALK ABOUT IT, BE
ABOUT IT, EVERYDAY I SEQUEL ♪
♪ IF I GOT IT THEN YOU KNOW YOU
GOT IT, HEAVEN, I CAN REACH YOU♪
♪ PET DOG, PET DOG, PET DOG,
MY DOG, THAT'S ALL ♪
♪ PICK BACK AND CHAT,
I TRAP THE BACK FOR Y'ALL ♪
♪ I RAP, I BLACK ON TRACK
SO REST ASSURED ♪
♪ MY RIGHTS, MY WRONGS I
WRITE 'TIL I'M RIGHT WITH GOD ♪
♪ WOULDN'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ WE BEEN HURT,
BEEN DOWN BEFORE ♪
♪ NIGGA,
WHEN OUR PRIDE WAS LOW ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT THE WORLD LIKE,
"WHERE DO WE GO?" ♪
♪ NIGGA, AND WE HATE PO-PO ♪
♪ WANNA KILL US DEAD IN
THE STREET FO SHO ♪
♪ NIGGA,
I'M AT THE PREACHER'S DOOR ♪
♪ MY KNEES GETTIN' WEAK
AND MY GUN MIGHT BLOW ♪
♪ BUT WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT
NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU
FEEL ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ NIGGA, WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ HUH? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ DO YOU HEAR ME, DO YOU
FEEL ME? WE GON' BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ I KEEP MY HEAD UP HIGH ♪
♪ I CROSS MY HEART AND
HOPE TO DIE ♪
♪ LOVIN' ME IS COMPLICATED ♪
♪ TOO AFRAID,
A LOT OF CHANGES ♪
♪ I'M ALRIGHT AND
YOU'RE A FAVORITE ♪
♪ DARK NIGHTS IN MY PRAYERS ♪
♪ I REMEMBERED
YOU WAS CONFLICTED ♪
♪ MISUSING YOUR INFLUENCE,
SOMETIMES I DID THE SAME ♪
♪ ABUSING MY POWER FULL
OF RESENTMENT ♪
♪ RESENTMENT THAT TURNED
INTO A DEEP DEPRESSION ♪
♪ FOUND MYSELF SCREAMIN'
IN THE HOTEL ROOM ♪
♪ I DIDN'T WANNA
SELF DESTRUCT ♪
♪ THE EVILS OF LUCY WAS
ALL AROUND ME ♪
♪ SO I WENT
RUNNIN' FOR ANSWERS ♪